The 100 이전 줄거리
By [WOW]Az-전타우랜
기미갤(수정 및 무단게시&배포 금지)
Previously on "The 100"...
너희 골수가 우리를
지상으로 다시 보낼 수 있다면
Your bone marrow can get
us back to the ground.
그들은 그만두지 않을 거야
They'll never stop.
그들은 그만두지 않을 거다
그녀가 거래를 했어요
우리가 이겼어요
She took the deal. We've won.
그들이 항복한 건가요?
They're surrendering?
꼭 그렇지만은 않아
Not quite.
아크 포로들은 어떻게 합니까?
What about prisoners from the Ark?
모두 죽을 거예요
They'll all be killed,
하지만 지휘관님은 그건
관심도 없으시죠, 그렇죠?
but you don't care about that, do you?
내 사람들을 지키는
의무가 우선이다
The duty to protect my people comes first.
퇴각나팔을 불어라
_
제가 그들을 돕겠습니다
Let me help them.
그를 끌고 가라
_
여기에 나를 두고 가지 마요
Please don't leave me here.
이렇게 끝낼 수는 없어
It can't be over.
선조들은 세상을
파괴하기 위하여
Our ancestors used a missile
미사일을 사용했었지
to destroy the world.
돌아가기 위해
하나를 사용할 거야
We're gonna use one to get back to it.
나와 함께 이것을
뛰어넘어보자, 존 머피
Take this leap of faith
with me, John Murphy.
이건 우리의 운명이다
This is our destiny.
도대체 저건 뭐죠?
What the hell is that?
무인비행기야
우리는 따라갈 거야
It's a drone. We're gonna follow it.
빛의 도시는 저기 밖에 있다
The City of Light is out there,
그리고 우리는 찾으러 갈 거다
and we are gonna find it.
그러니 배에 타
Now get in the boat.
아합
Yo, Ahab.
이리 오셔서, 좀 쉬세요
Come back. Get some rest.
괜찮다
I'm fine.
망할 노 같으니
Oh, screw this.
만약 주무시지 않을 거면
If you're not gonna sleep,
의장님이 저으세요
you can row.
노를 다시 들어, 크레이그
Get back on that oar, Craig.
안 들면 어쩌실 건데요?
Or what?
심지어 지금 올바른 방향으로
We don't even know if we're going
가고 있는지조차 모르잖아요
in the right direction anymore.
광활한 바다를 건너
무인비행기를 따라가고 있었잖아요
We followed that drone
across the open ocean.
여기서 죽어도
이상할 게 없다고요
Hell, we deserve to die out here.
알았어요, 알았어요
준비됐어요, 제가 저을게요
It's ok, it's ok. I'm
good to go. I can row.
육지?
Land?
육지야!
Land!
Yeah!
빛의 섬은 어떤가, 존?
How does an Island of Light
sound to you, John, huh?
- Oh!
- Damn it!
빌어먹을!
저게 뭐였지?
What was that?
노를 건지게
Get that oar. Get that oar.
리처즈! 물속에 뭐가 있어요!
Richards! There's something in the water!
노!
The oar!
제 팔이, 제 팔이...
My arm. Oh, my arm.
보이지 않아
어디에 있어?
I don't see it. Where is it?
리처즈! 리처즈!
Richards! Richards!
도대체 저건 뭐였죠?
What the hell was that thing?
당장 노가 필요하네
We need to row now.
돌아왔어, 기다리게!
It's back. Hold on!
- 어디에 있죠?
- 크레이그, 젓게
- Where is it?
- Craig, row.
- 젓게, 크레이그
- 어디에 있죠?
- Row, Craig!
- Where is it?
저으라고, 저으란 말이세!
Craig, row!
침몰하고 있어요
We're gonna sink.
모두 죽을 거예요
We're all gonna die. We're all gonna die.
제가 할 수 있어요
노을 저을 수 있어요
I can do it. I can row.
가서, 저으란 말이야!
Go! Row!
Aah!
도대체 의장님은
뭐가 문제예요?
Hey, what the hell is wrong with you?
놔요! 놔요!
Get off of me! Get off of me!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
도대체 뭐가...
What the hell is...
도대체 의장님은
뭐가 문제예요?
what the hell is wrong with you?
기다려
Hold on.
갔어, 갔다고
It's gone. Let's go.
왜 그러신 거죠?
Why?
그래야 우리가 살 수 있으니깐
So we could live.
그리고 넌 노를
저을 수 있기 때문이지
And because you can row.
By [WOW]Az-전타우랜
상업적이용 및 무단게시&수정&배포금지
최신수정버전은 기미갤에서
By [WOW]Az-전타우랜
상업적이용 및 무단게시&수정&배포금지
최신수정버전은 기미갤에서
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
때가 됐군
It's about time.
폭스
Fox.
옥타비아
Octavia.
안 가고 있었구나
You stayed.
엿먹어
당연히 있어야지
Screw you. Of course I stayed.
내 충성이 어디에 있어야
할지 정도는 안다고
I know where my loyalties lie.
들어가야 해
We have to get in there.
만약 그게 가능했다면
If that was possible,
여전히 내가 여기 밖에
있었을 거로 생각해?
do you think I'd still be out here?
왜 렉사가 퇴각나팔을 불었지?
Why did Lexa sound the retreat?
마운트 웨더와 그라운더들을
She made a deal with Mount Weather,
풀어주는 거래를 했어
그러니 우리는 스스로 해결해야 해
freed the Grounders, and now we're on own.
그만해!
여깄는 걸 알게 될 거야
Stop! They'll know we're here.
링컨은 어찌 되었어?
What about Lincoln? There's no way he
이와 같은 계획에
동의했을 리가 없어
would have gone along
with a plan like this.
동의하지 않았어
그래서 끌려갔어
He didn't, they took him.
너 왜 그래?
What's wrong with you?
저 문을 통과하려는 거잖아
I am getting through that door.
그게 네 계획이야?
And that's your plan?
오빠는 너만 믿고 있어
Bellamy's counting on you.
모두가 언제나
너만 믿고 있다고
Everyone's always counting on you.
그래서 내게 바라는 게 뭔데?
Well, what do you want from me?
넌 렉사를 믿었어
You trusted Lexa.
톤디씨에 폭탄이
떨어지게 방관했어
You let a bomb drop on Tondc.
모든 사람들이...
You let all those people...
할 수 있는
최선을 다한 거야!
I am doing the best I can!
그래? 그런데 어쩌지
그 정도로는 안 되는데 말이야
Yeah? Well, it's not good enough.
Oh, Bellamy.
오빠
그럴 줄 알았어
I knew it.
너희 둘은 구멍을 뚫기엔
너무 말랐다니깐
You two are too scrawny to drill.
Hey.
Ohh! Heh.
괜찮아, 우리 편이야
It's all right. She's with us.
군대는 어딨어?
Where's your army?
너처럼 방금 떠났어
Gone just like yours.
계획이 있다면 말해봐
Say you have a plan.
딱히 없어
단테랑 얘기해야 해
Not really. We need to talk to Dante.
격리되어 있다고
마야가 그러더군
Maya says he's in quarantine.
클라크!
Clarke!
고마워
Thank you.
30분 남았어
30 minutes.
교체해야 해
그럴 리 없는데
And we just changed
it. That can't be right.
Uh, shh... um...
마지막 산소통이야
It's her last tank.
저기, 다른 걸 찾아낼 거야
Hey. Uh, we'll find you another one.
여분의 산소는
전부 5층에 있어
All the supplemental oxygen is on level 5.
그러면 너를 5층으로 데려다 줄게
Then we have to get you to level 5.
5층은 우리 중 누구에게도
안전하지 않아
5 isn't safe for any of us.
쓰레기 활송장치를
다시 이용하면 될 거야
We'll take the trash chute again.
통할 거야
It will work.
들어가게 되면, 아마도
마야가 옳아
To get in, maybe. Maya's right.
마운틴에 모든 군인이
거기에 있을 거야
Every solider in this mountain is there.
도망칠 순 없을 거야
We'll never make it out.
할 수 있어
나뉘자
We can do this. We'll split up.
그래, 너희는 단테에게 가
Ok. You guys go for Dante.
우리는 마야를 도울게
We'll help Maya.
죄수를 볼 것이다
_
좀 자둬
어떻게 이럴 수 있습니까?
How could you do this?
지휘관님께 충성을 맹세했다
I swore loyalty to this commander.
지휘관님께서는 우리의 동맹이
살육되도록 내버려뒀어요
She left our allies to be slaughtered.
우리 모두에게 치욕이에요
She dishonors us all.
그리고 네 거역도 불명예스럽지
And your disobedience dishonors you.
왜 여기 오신 거죠, 인드라?
Why are you here, Indra?
왜냐하면 너도 역시
트리의 일원이기 때문이다
Because you are also tree crew.
그냥 그녀를 죽게
내버려둘 수가 없었다고요
I can't just let her die.
휴전 조건에 따르면
Under the terms of the truce,
마운틴 주위의 땅들은
출입이 금지되었다
the lands surrounding the
mountain are forbidden.
만약 이걸 깬다면
If you violate this,
지휘관님께서는 너를 다시
받아주지 않을 것이다
Lexa will never take you back.
옥타비아는 스스로
선택을 한 거다
Octavia made her choice.
지금 너도 스스로
선택을 해야 한다
Now you make yours.
- 여기 있다
- 고맙습니다
- You?
- Thank you.
대통령님, 에머슨 중위가
복귀했습니다
Sir, Lieutenant Emerson is back.
기숙사로 가보셔야겠습니다
You're needed in the dorm.
알았네
Ok.
Oh! Oh! Aah!
무릎 꿇고 있어
On their knees.
Oh! Oh, god! Oh! Oh!
꿇어
Down.
병력 손실이 있나?
We take any losses?
그들만큼 많지는 않습니다, 대통령님
Not as many as they did, Sir.
하지만 제가 치유된 병력 중 유일하게
남아있는 사람인 게 유감입니다
I'm afraid I'm the only
one left who's been cured.
아이들 중 일부는
여전히 찾지 못했습니다
Some of the kids are still missing.
괜찮으시다면, 방호복을
입은 팀을 데리고 가서
If you'd like, I'll take a team in hazmats
다른 층들을 쓸어버리겠습니다
and sweep the other levels.
아니네, 더는 병력을
낭비할 필요는 없네
No. No more wasted lives.
48시간 후면, 우리는
모두 지상에 있을걸세
In 48 hours, we will all be on the ground.
복면을 벗기게
Take off the the hoods.
안돼
No.
- 아빠?
- 네이트!
- Dad?
- Nate!
Uh!
안돼! 이 개새끼들아!
Uh! No! You bastards!
사람들에게 무슨 짓을 하는 거죠?
What is wrong with you people?
제 딸은 어디에 있어요?
Where's my daughter?
클라크에 관해서
이야기하고 있습니다
She's talking about Clarke.
이렇게 돼서 유감이군
I'm sorry it had to come to this.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
- 죽었어
- 괜찮아
- He's dead.
- That's ok.
이미 골수를 전부 얻었어
We've already got all of the marrow.
경비, 다른 사람이 필요하네
Guards, we need another one.
저 여자가 다음이다
She's next.
안돼, 안돼, 날 데려가
건드리지 마
No. No. Take me. Don't touch her!
건드리지 말라고!
- Don't touch her!
- Get off.
건드리지 마!
건드리지 말라고!
Don't touch her! Don't touch her!
제발, 안돼
Please. No. Oh!
좋아, 묶어
All right. Get a strap.
가자
Let's go.
제발, 제발 그러지 마요
Please. Please don't.
- Huh!
- Yaagh!
잡아! 눕혀!
Hold her! Hold her down!
안돼! 이거 놔!
No! Get off me!
Oh!
Please don't.
Uh...
No...
그만, 그만... 그만!
No, no... No!
잘 있었나, 클라크
Hello, Clarke.
대통령님, 다시 도움이 필요합니다
Sir, we need your help again.
괜찮아요
카메라는 복도에 있는
It's ok. I took out the camera
접속 배선함에서 제거했어요
from the junction box in the hall.
자유롭게 말해도 돼요
We can talk freely.
어쨌든, 아무도
못 보는 거구나
No one's watching, anyway.
너희 덕분에
그들 모두 5층에 있구먼
Thanks to you, they're all on level 5.
- 대통령님은 아니시죠
- 그래, 난 아니라네
- You're not.
- No. I'm not.
부탁합니다
시간이 얼마 없습니다
Please. We don't have much time.
마운틴에서 모두를 죽이지 않고
We need a way to get our
people out of this mountain
사람들을 빠져나가게 할
방법이 필요합니다
without killing everyone.
돕지 않을 거야
He's not gonna help us.
전력을 끊어서
마운틴에 있는
You cut the power, risking the lives
모든 사람의 목숨을
위태롭게 했다
of everyone in this mountain...
내 사람들, 심지어 너희를
도와줬던 사람까지도 말이다
my people, even the ones who helped you.
5층은 안전할 거라는 걸
이미 알고 있었어요
We knew they'd be safe on level 5.
수리할 수 있도록
We made sure not to destroy the turbines
터빈을 파괴하지는 않았어요
so you could repair them.
여기서 우리는 좋은 사람들이에요
당신들이 아니라요
We're the good guys here, not you.
말해 보렴, 그럼
만약 너희 사람들과
Tell me, if we released your people
그들을 풀어준다면
내게는 무슨 일이 생기겠니?
and theirs, what would've happened to mine?
지휘 본부에 우리를
들어가게 할 수 있니?
Can you get us into the command center?
5층에서 무슨 일이
일어나는지 볼 필요가 있어
We need to see what's happening on level 5.
- 문제없어
- 갑시다
- No problem.
- Let's go.
저희를 도와야 할 겁니다
You're gonna help us,
좋아하건 말건 말입니다
whether you like it or not.
저건...
That's...
존, 내가 돕도록 해주게
John, let me help you.
의장님에게선 어떤 도움도
원하지 않아요
I don't want anything from you.
어서, 넌 생존자야
Come on. You're a survivor.
우리 둘 다
We both are.
기분이 나아지게 하시려고 스스로
Whatever you have to tell yourself
무슨 말이든 하시는군요, 의장님
feel better, Chancellor.
우리의 운명이...
저기에 있네, 존
Our destiny... is out there, John.
그러면 크레이그의
운명은 어찌하고요?
And what about Craig's destiny?
다수를 구하기 위해
소수를 희생한 거였네
We sacrificed a few to save the many.
있잖아요, 의장님이 옳아요
You know, you're right.
정확하게 말씀드리자면
I am a survivor...
의장님을 따라가는 걸 그만둔
which is exactly why
생존자죠
I am done following you.
제 길을 갈 거예요
I'll go my own way.
의장님은 본인이
원하시는 길로 가세요
You can go whichever the hell way you want.
존, 존!
John. John!
제게서 떨어지세요
Get the hell away from me.
너무 많은 피를 흘렸어
그리고 여전히 흘리고 있다고!
You lost too much blood. Be still!
저거 들리나?
Did you hear that? Huh.
부탁합니다, 당신이
누구시든 도움이 필요합니다
Please, whoever you are, we need your help.
기다려요!
Wait! Wait!
존
John...
안 되겠어요,
그냥 가세요, 아시겠어요?
I can't make it. Just go, all right?
의장님이 원하시는 걸
우리 둘 다 알잖아요
We both know you want to.
돌아오겠네, 존
I'll come back for you, John.
너희 약속의 땅은 엿 같아!
Your promised land sucks!
말했잖은가
여기는 아무도 없다고
I told you, there's no one here.
우리가 대통령님의 말씀을
믿지 못하는 건 유감이에요
Sorry if we don't take your word for it.
왜 대통령님은 사람들과
5층에 계시지 않은 건가요?
Why aren't you with your people on level 5?
내가 한 짓으로 그들은 자유로워졌지만
난 그럴 수 없었네
After what I've done,
they can be free. I can't.
해방에는 대가가 따르는 법이지
Deliverance comes at a cost.
그들이 치를 필요는 없기에
내가 짊어진걸세
I bear it so they don't have to.
케이지가 아니었어
(전대통령 아들, 현재 대통령)
It wasn't Cage.
그라운더와 거래를 하게 한 건
대통령님 생각이셨군요
It was your idea to make
the deal with the Grounders.
열었어, 들어가도 돼
We're in. Got it.
아무도 없어, 대통령님이
사실을 말씀하신 게 맞는군요
It's clear. He's telling the truth.
좋았어
Ok.
모니터를 준비하자
Let's get the monitors up.
어서, 서둘러야 해
산소가 바닥이 났어
Come on. We have to
hurry. She's out of air.
먼저 그 문을 닫아야 해
First, you need to close the door.
여유 시간이네
Time to spare.
그녀는 안전해졌어
그만 우리는 이제 갈까?
She's safe. Could we go now?
괜찮을 거야
I'll be ok.
이봐, 널 남기고 떠날 순 없어
Look. I'm not leaving you.
- 재스퍼 - 살아야 있는 거지
안전한 건 아니란 말이야
- Jasper.
- She's alive, but she's not safe.
케이지는 내가
너희를 도운 걸 알아
Cage knows I helped you guys.
그는 5층에 있어
He's on level 5.
그러면 우리는 뭘 해야 하지?
So what do we do?
케이지를 죽이자
We kill Cage.
나도 낄게
I'm in.
메인 센터는 여전히
작동하는 거 같아
I think main center's live.
맙소사
Oh, my god.
저거 레이븐이야?
Is that Raven?
엄마
Mom.
멈추라고 당장 말씀하세요
Tell them to stop now.
그런 일은 절대 없을 거다
I won't do that.
에머슨
Emerson.
마운트 웨더 보안요원
Carl Emerson, Mount Weather
칼 에머슨, 응답하세요
security detail, come in.
누구냐?
Who is this?
누군지 아시잖아요
You know who it is.
대통령에게 무전기를 드리세요
Give the radio to the president.
그들이 움직이고 있어
They're moving.
문제 될 건 없어
Not a problem.
주 모니터로 가져올게
I'll bring it on main monitor.
대통령 월레스다
This is President Wallace.
당신의 아버지를 데리고 있어요
I have your father.
만약 제 사람들을 풀어주지 않는다면
If you don't let my people go,
죽이겠어요
I'll kill him.
데리고 있다는 걸
어떻게 알지?
How do I know you have him?
그대로 계속하거라, 케이지
Stay the course, Cage.
그러지 못할 거야
You won't do it.
당신은 절
잘 알지 못하잖아요
You don't know me very well.
이제 끝내죠
제 사람들을 풀어줘요
This ends now. Release my people.
그럴 수는 없다
I can't do that.
그건 우리 사람들의 끝을
의미하는 거다, 클라크
It would mean the end
of our people, Clarke.
클라크, 우린 그가 필요해
Clarke, we need him.
그리고 그의 아들이
나를 믿기를 원하지
And I need his son to believe me.
제가 이걸
하게 하지 마세요
Don't make me do this.
아빠
Dad...
우리 사람들을 보살필게요
I'll take care of our people.
우리 중 누구도 이 시점에서는
선택권이 없구나, 클라크
None of us has a choice here, Clarke.
이걸 원하진 않았어요
I didn't want this.
나도 그렇단다
Neither did I.
Oh! Uh...
정말 신중하게
제 말을 들으세요
Listen to me very carefully.
제 사람들이 풀려날 때까지
멈추지 않을 거예요
I will not stop until my people are free.
만약 풀어주지 않는다면...
If you don't let them go...
5층에 방사선을 노출할 거예요
I will irradiate level 5.
케이지, 제 말 들으세요
Cage, listen to me.
다른 누군가가
죽기를 원하지 않아요
I don't want anyone else to die.
드릴을 멈추면
얘기할 수 있어요
Stop the drilling, and we can talk.
우리 모두 이 상황을
피할 방법이 있을 거예요
There must be a way to
get us all out of this.
- 에머슨
- 네, 대통령님
- Emerson.
- Sir.
지휘 본부에서
우리를 보고 있네
They're watching us
from the command center.
가서 모두 죽이게
Go kill them all.
네, 대통령님
Yes, Sir.
에머슨이 우리를
해치우려고 오고 있어
Emerson is coming for us.
그들은 내 키 카드를 비활성화시켰어
에머슨 것도 그렇게 할 수 있어?
They deactivated my key
card. Can you do that to his?
그건 쉽지
That one's easy.
어디로 가고 있는 거지?
Where's he going?
기숙사
The dorm.
몬티, 할 수 있어? 저쪽 층에
방사선을 노출할 수 있어?
Monty, can you do it? Can
you irradiate the level?
할 수 있어
I can do it.
잠깐 기다려봐, 클라크, 이것에
대해서는 좀 더 생각할 필요가 있어
Wait a second, Clarke. We
need to think about this.
거기에는 애들도 있다고...
There are kids in there...
알아
I know.
그리고 우리를
도왔던 사람들도 있어
And people who helped us.
그럼 제발 더 나은 생각이
있으면 좀 주지 않을래?
Then please give me a better idea.
이 사람을 치우게
Take that one off the table.
- 대통령님, 아직 다 못했습니다
- 당장!
- Sir, we're not done.
- Now!
- 저 여자를 테이블 위에 눕히게
- 안돼
- Put her on it.
- No.
안돼요, 제발요, 이봐요!
이걸 할 필요는 없잖아요
No. Please. Hey! You don't have to do this.
멈춰!
Stop!
다른 방법이 있을 거예요
There has to be another way.
- 그런 건 없어
- 안돼
- There isn't.
- No.
내가 무슨 짓을 한 거지?
What have I done?
골수 때문에 누군가
죽을 필요는 없어요
No one has to die for bone marrow.
기증할게요
We can donate it. We can donate it.
묶어
Strap her down.
다치게 하지 마!
Don't hurt her!
안돼
No.
이봐요, 기증할 수 있다니깐요!
Hey, we can donate it!
그럴 일은 없을 거야
That'll never happen.
할 수 있어요, 그녀의 도움이 있으면
그걸 가능하게 할 수 있어요
I can. I can make it happen with her help.
우리 모두 살아남을 수 있다고요
We can all survive.
우린 그럴 순 없어
We can't.
구멍 뚫기 작업을 진행하겠습니다
Proceed with the drilling.
침착하게
Steady.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
클라크, 만약 이걸 한다면
더는 되돌릴 수 없어
Clarke, if we do this,
there is no going back.
확인해보자
Figure it out.
너무 오래 걸려
This is taking too long.
내 말은...
잡혔으면 어쩌지?
I mean, what if she got caught?
그럼 어떤 소리라도 들렸을 거야
We'd have heard something.
게다가 리 병장을 찾지
못했다면 어쩌지? 혹은...
Then what if she couldn't
find Sergeant Lee or...
잘은 모르지만...
프로토콜이 바뀐 거라면?
I don't know... the protocol changed?
잡혔으면 어쩌지?
What if he got caught?
재스퍼, 전사는
Jasper, a warrior doesn't worry
통제할 수 없는 것에
대해서는 걱정하지 않아
about what he can't control.
오, 다행이다
Oh, thank god.
본 사람은 없고?
Anyone see you?
리, 총 내려놔
Lee, put down the gun.
네가 아웃사이더랑 있다고
말하진 않았잖아
You didn't say there
was an outsider with you.
아웃사이더가 아니야
She's not an outsider.
- 그래, 맞아
- 우리 편이야
- Yes, she is.
- She's with us.
케이지는 기숙사에 있어
Cage is in the dorms.
골수를 더 채취하기 위해서
아크에서 또 다른 무리를 끌고 왔어
They brought another group
in from the Ark, more marrow.
심지어 댐은
수리하려고 하지도 않아
They're not even trying to fix the dam.
케이지와 있는 병력이
몇 명이나 되지?
How many soldiers with Cage?
6명이야, 왜?
Uh, 6. Why?
그냥 나를 데려가
Just get me close.
또 다른 8명분의 투여량을
찾게 돼서 기뻐할 거야
They'll be happy you found another 8 doses.
필요한 게...
I need a...
목구멍을 노려
Aim for the throat.
그어버려, 찌르지 말고
깊숙하게 그어버려
Slash. Don't stab. Make it deep.
뭘 하는지 알고 있길 바란다
I hope you know what you're doing.
나도 역시 그래
Me, too.
- 해낼 거야
- 그래
- You got this.
- Yeah.
사랑해
I love you.
♪ if you hear him howling
around your kitchen door ♪
♪ better not let him in ♪
♪ little, old lady got
mutilated late last night ♪
♪ werewolves of London again ♪
♪ ah-hoo ♪
♪ werewolves of London ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ He's a hairy-handed gent ♪
♪ who ran amuck in Kent ♪
♪ lately, he's been... ♪
약속의 땅이라
Promised land.
♪ Overheard in Mayfair ♪
♪ you better stay away from him ♪
♪ he'll rip your lungs out, Jim ♪
♪ ha! I'd like to meet his tailor ♪
♪ ah-hoo ♪
♪ werewolves of London ♪
아크에서는 먼 길이었지?
Long way from the Ark, huh?
내 아크가 아니야
Not my Ark.
난 어느 쪽도 아니야
I didn't have a view, either.
여전히, 그걸 볼 수 있기를 원해
Still, I wish I could see it.
아마 볼 수 있을 거야
거기엔 에어락이 있어
Maybe you can. There's an airlock.
에머슨을 잡아두는데
그걸 이용했어
We used it to hold Emerson.
우리가 해야 할 건 단지 그곳으로
널 데려가는 거지, 그리고...
All we have to do is get you there, and...
그래서 나보고 감방에서 살라고?
so I could live in a cell?
적어도 살 수는 있잖아
At least you could live.
아웃사이더다!
Outsiders!
안돼, 옥타비아! 그러지마!
No, Octavia! Don't!
안돼
No.
아웃사이더예요, 우리 뒤에...
Outsiders! Behind us.
Uh!
Ugh! Ugh...
이동! 가, 가!
Move! Go, go!
저기서 빠져나오게 해야 해
They got to get out of there.
마야 비, 꼼짝하지 마!
Maya Vie, stop!
도망쳐!
Run!
당장!
Now!
그가 여기에 있어
He's here.
재스퍼야, 그들이 끌고 갔어
Jasper. They caught him.
또 다른 한 명을 잡았습니다
We got another one.
재스퍼!
Jasper!
왜 이러는 거야?
Why are you doing this?
식당에 위기조치 대응반을 보내
Response team to the mess hall.
흩어져!
Spread out!
꼼짝하지 마, 손들어
Stop. Hands up.
왜 멈추는 거야?
Why are you stopping?
왜냐하면 다 했거든
Because I did it.
우리가 해야 할 건...
이걸 당기는 것뿐이야
All we have to do... is pull this.
그러면 해치와
통풍구가 열릴 거야
Hatches and vents will open,
그러면 스크러버가 역회전해서
바깥 공기가 들어오게 돼
and the scrubbers reverse,
pulling in outside air
문을 날려버리려고 해
he's gonna blow the door.
클라크, 시간이 없어
Clarke, we're out of time.
엎드려
Down now.
나의 여동생
나의 책임
My sister. My responsibility.
그들을 구해야 해
I have to save them.
함께 하자
Together.
- 저지하게
- 네, 대통령님
- Restrain him.
- Yes, Sir.
움직이지 마!
Don't move!
뭐지?
What is it?
뭐... 뭐야?
What is... what is this?
여기서 나가!
Get out of here!
안돼
No.
마야
Maya.
재스퍼, 돌아와!
Jasper, come back!
이봐, 풀어줘!
Hey, set us free!
안돼, 안돼, 안돼, 안돼!
No, no, no, no!
재스퍼...
Jasper...
나 여기 있어
I'm here.
마야는 죄가 없어
She was innocent.
우리 중 누구도
죄 없는 자는 없어
None of us is innocent.
안돼, 안돼
No. No.
안돼
No.
맙소사, 안돼
Oh, god. No.
우리 사람들을 데리러 가자
Let's go get our people.
- 옥타비아
- 옥타비아, 서둘러
- Octavia.
- Octavia, hurry.
이봐, 그 경비에게서
키를 가져다주렴
Hey, get the keys from the guard.
I can't believe this.
어서
Come on.
잠깐만 기다리세요
Hang on.
There!
이것에서 날 좀 빼줘
Get me out of these things.
괜찮아요
Ok.
클라크는 어디에 있죠?
Where's Clarke?
뭘 한 거야?
What did you do?
선택권이 없었어
We had no choice.
케이지를 이제 막
죽이려던 참이었는데
I was gonna kill Cage.
단지 1분만 더 시간을 줬더라면
If you'd just given me one more minute,
끝낼 수 있었어
it would've been over.
재스퍼, 그들은 절대
멈추지 않았을 거야
Jasper, they never would've stopped.
기숙사로 돌아가야 해
We have to go to the dorm.
어떻게 이런 일이
일어나도록 내버려둔 거야?
How could you let this happen?
미안해
I'm sorry.
미안해?
미안하다고?
Sorry? You're sorry?
그래
All right. Ok.
엄마
Mom.
노력은 했어요
I tried.
좋은 사람이 되려고
노력은 했다고요
I tried to be the good guy.
아마도 좋은 사람들이란
없는가 보다
Maybe there are no good guys.
하퍼!
Harper!
잘했네
You did good.
자, 사람들을
집으로 데리고 가자
Now let's get these people home.
네, 그러죠
Yes, Sir.
케이지는 어디에 있죠?
Where's Cage?
거기 누구야?
Who's there?
모습을 들어내
Show yourself.
네게 줄 게 있어
I got something for you.
이건 널 위한 거야
This is for you.
안돼
No.
최초의 투약이 최악이지
The first dose is the worst.
들어오는 동안
Get security on the perimeter
주변을 경계하라!
while they're coming in!
돌아왔어!
They're back!
애비!
Abby!
잠시만 멈춰요
Wait.
재스퍼
Jasper.
깜빡 잊을 뻔했어
I almost forgot.
내 고글이네
My goggles.
고마워
Thank you.
한잔할 자격이
있다고 생각하는데
I think we deserve a drink.
나도 한잔 갖다 줘
Have one for me.
이봐, 만약 우리가
이걸 이겨낸다면...
Hey, if we can get through this...
들어가지 않을 거야
I'm not going in.
저기, 용서가 필요한 거라면
Look. If you need forgiveness,
내가 용서해줄게
I'll give that to you.
넌 용서받은 거야
You're forgiven.
제발 안으로 들어가자
Please come inside.
날 위해 그들을 보살펴줘
Take care of them for me.
- 클라크
- 안돼
- Clarke...
- No.
매일 그들의 얼굴 보면
Seeing their faces every day is just gonna
방금 내가 한 짓이
떠오를 거야
remind me of what I did to get them here.
우리가 한 거였어
What we did.
이걸 혼자서 할 필요는 없어
You don't have to do this alone.
그들이 치를 필요는 없기에
내가 짊어질 거야
I bear it so they don't have to.
어디로 가려고?
Where you gonna go?
모르겠어
I don't know.
다시 만날지도 몰라
May we meet again.
다시 만날지도 모르지
그녀를 멈추려고 노력했어...
I tried to stop her...
하지만 난 정신을 잃었어
but I lost control.
그녀는 발사 코드를 가져갔어
She got the launch codes.
그녀였어, 그녀가 했어...
It was her. She did it...
하지만 그건 내 잘못이었어
but it was my fault.
미안해
I'm sorry.
정말 정말 미안해
I'm so, so sorry.
갈수록 신기하구먼
Curiouser and curiouser.
환영해요, 델로니어스
Welcome, Thelonious.
해내셨다니 기쁘군요
기다리고 있었어요
I'm glad you made it. I've been waiting.
누구시죠?
Who are you?
제 이름은 앨리예요
My name is Alie.
어떻게 제 이름을 아는 거죠?
How do you know my name?
델로니어스
좋은 이름이시네요
Thelonious. It's a good name.
이중적 의미가 있죠
It has a double meaning.
그리스인들에게는 델로니어스는
To the Greeks, Thelonious
영주 또는 통치자를 뜻했죠
meant lord or ruler.
독일인들에게는
땅의 새싹을 의미했고요
To the Germans, it meant
tiller of the earth.
당신은 어느 쪽인지 궁금하군요
Which are you, I wonder.
나를 기다리고 있었다고 말씀하셨죠
You said you were waiting for me.
오랫동안요
For ages,
아니, 그런 것 같아요
or so it seems.
시간이 제게는 다르게 흘려가죠
Time passes differently for me.
아주 좋아요, 델로니어스
Very good, Thelonious.
기대했던 만큼
통찰력이 있으시군요
You're as perceptive as I had hoped.
진짜가 아니군요
You're not real.
"진짜"를 정의하자면
Define "real."
당신의 그릇은
탄소를 기반으로 하죠
Your vessel is carbon-based.
제 것은 실리콘이에요
Mine is silicon.
당신의 사고는 화학 작용으로
일어나지만, 제 것은 디지털이죠
Your thoughts are
chemical. Mine are digital.
여기가 나의 목적지였다고 생각했어요
And I thought this was my destination.
맞아요, 델로니어스
It is, Thelonious.
따라오세요
Follow me.
당신은 여기로 올 예정이셨어요
You were meant to come here.
당신의 선물을
받았을 때, 알게 됐죠
I realized it when I received your gift.
제 선물이라고요?
My gift?
저를 위해 아래로 가져오신 거
감사해요, 델로니어스
Thank you for bringing it
down for me, Thelonious.
우리는 해야 할 일이 있어요
We have work to do.
By [WOW]Az-전타우랜
상업적이용 및 무단게시&수정&배포금지
최신수정버전은 기미갤에서
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -